Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
- Series XII. Printed Material
  - Wartime Emergency Bulletins
    - How to Cook Poultry, December 1942 (Box 46)
    - Mental Health in Wartime, January 1943 (Box 46)
    - Vegetables in Victory Meals, January 1943 (Box 46)
    - Care and Adjustment of the Sewing Machine, February 1943 (Box 46)
    - Bread and Whole-Grain Cereals, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - The Food Supply for the Family, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Convenience in Canning and in Storing Canned Food, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - When Children are Together, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Simple Repairs of Upholstered Furniture, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Simple Repairs of Wood Furniture, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Varieties of Vegetables and Fruits for Freezing, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Save Bedding I, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Saving Bedding II, March 1943 (Box 46)
    - Curing Meats, May 1943 (Box 46)
    - College catalog, 1920 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Quizzes that accompany bulletins, 1901 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Quizzes that accompany bulletins, 1902 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Quizzes that accompany bulletins, 1903 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Circular giving information about the Cornell Farmers' Reading-Course. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Volumes
    - Records, Faculty of Home Economics; Volume 1: 1925-1929; Volume II: 1929-1933 (Box 47)
    - Appraising the College Program in Home Economics: A Study of Some Procedures. Ruth T. Lehman, 1950 (Box 47)
    - Aesthetic Education. Charles DeGarmo, 1913. Cornell Study Bulletins for Teachers, no. 6 (Box 47)
    - Art and the Formation of Taste. Lucy Crane, Chautauqua Library Garnet Series, 1885 (Box 47)
    - Trip Around the World. Marion Pfund and Beulah Blackmore, 1936 (Box 47)
    - Letters from Belgium. Flora Rose and Martha Van Rensselaer, 1923 (Box 47)
    - Specification of Labor and Materials Required for Home Economics Building., July 18, 1931 (Box 47)
    - A Study of 952 Graduates of the New York State College of Home Economics. Cornell University, 1911-1930 (Box 47)
  - Cornell Rural School Leaflets
    - Hints on Making Collections of Insects-Teacher's Leaflets, April 1898 (Box 66)
    - Nature Study Syllabus, December 1909 (Box 66)
    - September 1910 (Box 66)
    - March 1914 (Box 66)
    - Greetings, November 1914 (Box 66)
    - January 1915 (Box 66)
    - March 1915 (Box 66)
    - Rural School Leaflet Plan for 1915-1916, September 1915 (Box 66)
    - Rural School Leaflet Plan for 1916-1917, September 1916 (Box 66)
    - The Nature Study of Streams and Ponds, March 1920 (Box 66)
    - An Index, 1920-1931 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, January 1921 (Box 104)
    - Rural School Leaflet Plan for 1921-1922, September 1921 (Box 66)
    - Woody Plants in Autumn, November 1921 (Box 104)
    - The Earth and Its Weather, January 1922 (Box 104)
    - Amphibia and Reptilia, March 1922 (Box 104)
    - The Greatest Show on Earth, November 1922 (Box 104)
    - Winter Birds, January 1923 (Box 104)
    - Spring Flowers, March 1923 (Box 104)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1923 (Box 66)
    - Camp Fires and Camp Cookery, November 1923 (Box 66)
    - Woody Plants in Winter, January 1924 (Box 66)
    - Shore Birds And Game Birds, January 1924 (Box 66)
    - Shore Birds and Game Birds, November 1924 (Box 104)
    - Pests of Plants, Pets and People, January 1925 (Box 66, 104)
    - Cultivated Plants, March 1925 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1925 (Box 66)
    - Rural School Leaflet Plan for 1925-1926, September 1925 (Box 66)
    - Larger Mammals, November 1925 (Box 66)
    - Rock Stories, January 1926 (Box 66)
    - Moth and Butterflies, March 1926 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1926 (Box 66)
    - Babes in the Woods, November 1926 (Box 66)
    - House Plants, January 1927 (Box 66)
    - Domestic Birds, March 1927 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1927 (Box 66)
    - Fungi, November 1927 (Box 66)
    - Rocks and Minerals, January 1928 (Box 66)
    - How Things Move and Are Moved, March 1928 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1928 (Box 104)
    - Liverworts, Mosses, Ferns, and their Kin, November 1928 (Box 66)
    - Domestic Mammals, January 1929 (Box 66)
    - A Travelog of Birds, March 1929 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1929 (Box 66)
    - Through the Year, November 1929 (Box 66)
    - The Sky at Night, January 1930 (Box 66)
    - The Flowers of Woody Plants, March 1930 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1930 (Box 104)
    - Fall Weeds, November 1930 (Box 104)
    - Earth Forms, January 1931 (Box 66)
    - How Flora and Fauna Care for Their Young, March 1931 (Box 66)
    - Leaflet Service for 1931-1932, September 1931 (Box 66)
    - Fall Insects, November 1931 (Box 66)
    - In the Woods in Winter, January 1932 (Box 66)
    - Garden Flowers, March 1932 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1932 (Box 66)
    - Poisons, Diseases, Medicines, November 1932 (Box 66)
    - Light, January 1933 (Box 66)
    - The Marsh in Spring, March 1933 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1933 (Box 66)
    - Fields in Fall, November 1933 (Box 66)
    - Sound, January 1934 (Box 66)
    - New Life, March 1934 (Box 66)
    - Leaflet Service for 1934-1935, September 1934 (Box 66)
    - Fruits of Woody Plants, November 1934 (Box 66)
    - Heat, January 1935 (Box 66)
    - Made of Earth, March 1935 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1935 (Box 66)
    - Weight, November 1935 (Box 66)
    - Conservation, January 1936 (Box 66)
    - Save the Soil, March 1936 (Box 66)
    - The Leaflet Service for 1936-1937, September 1936 (Box 66)
    - Spiders and Their Kin, November 1936 (Box 66)
    - What Happens When?, January 1937 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet for 1937-1938, September 1937 (Box 66)
    - The Sea, March 1937 (Box 66)
    - Are They Vermin?, November 1937 (Box 66)
    - Homes, January 1938 (Box 66)
    - Electricity and Magnetism, March 1938 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet for 1938-1939, September 1938 (Box 66)
    - Waterways in Fall, November 1938 (Box 66)
    - What's the Difference?, January 1939 (Box 66)
    - Creeping, Sprawling, Climbing Plants, March 1939 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1939 (Box 66)
    - Farm-Forest Facts, November 1939 (Box 66)
    - Fields in Winter, January 1940 (Box 66)
    - Waterways in Spring, March 1940 (Box 99)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet for 1940-1941, September 1940 (Box 66)
    - The Finer Side of Life, November 1940 (Box 66)
    - You, January 1941 (Box 66)
    - Outdoor Living, March 1941 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet for 1941-1942, September 1941 (Box 66)
    - Holes in the Ground, November 1941 (Box 99)
    - More About Water, January 1942 (Box 99)
    - U.S. Minerals and Us, March 1942 (Box 66)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1942 (Box 99)
    - Let's Play Safe, November 1942 (Box 99)
    - The Mystery and Mastery of the Air, January 1943 (Box 99)
    - Wild Foods, March 1943 (Box 99)
    - Cornell Rural School Leaflet, September 1943 (Box 99)
    - The Mastery of Water, November 1943 (Box 99)
    - Little Climates, January 1944 (Box 99)
    - Tools for Pounding and Cutting, March 1944 (Box 66)
    - Fibers, November 1944 (Box 66)
    - The Cornell Nature Study Philosophy, September 1944 (Box 66)
    - Over the Ground, January 1945 (Box 99, 104)
    - Cover, Spring 1945 (Box 99)
    - Window Laboratories, Fall 1945 (Box 99)
    - Let's See, Winter 1945-1946 (Box 99)
    - The Story of Conservation in New York, March 1946 (Box 99)
    - Outdoor Education, September 1946 (Box 99)
    - Hedgerows, Fall 1946 (Box 99)
    - Microbes, Winter 1946-1947 (Box 66)
    - More Outdoor Education, September 1947 (Box 99)
    - Wildfire, Fall 1947 (Box 99)
    - Snow, Frost, and Ice, Winter 1947-1948 (Box 99)
    - Apple Tree Animals, Spring 1948 (Box 99)
    - Lawn Laboratories, Fall 1948 (Box 99)
    - Wood, Winter 1948-1949 (Box 99)
    - Shell-Bearers, Spring 1948-1949 (Box 99)
    - The Elementary Science Library, September 1949 (Box 99)
    - Paved-Desert Laboratories, Fall 1949 (Box 99)
    - Hunters and Hunted, Winter 1949-1950 (Box 99)
    - Fish Bait, Spring 1950 (Box 99)
    - Nature Writings, September 1950 (Box 99)
    - Fish and Fishing, November 1950 (Box 99)
    - Winter Lunches for Wildlife, Winter 1950-1951 (Box 99)
    - Wooded Laboratories, Spring 1951 (Box 99)
    - Conservation- a handbook for teachers, September 1951 (Box 99)
    - Wet Laboratories, Fall 1951 (Box 99)
    - Survival in Winter, Winter 1952 (Box 99)
    - Reptiles, Spring 1952 (Box 99)
    - Teachers' Number, Fall 1952 (Box 66)
    - The Story of Conservation in New York, Fall 1952 (Box 104)
    - Inviting Bird Neighbors, Spring 1953 (Box 99)
    - Outdoor Nature Studies, Fall 1953 (Box 66)
    - Air Laboratories, Fall 1953 (Box 104)
    - Insect Homes, Winter 1953-1954 (Box 104)
    - Woodlands in Spring, Spring 1954 (Box 104)
    - Cornell Nature Study Leaflets, Fall 1956 (Box 99)
    - Beetles, Spring 1957 (Box 9104)
    - Electricity and Magnetism, Winter 1956-1957 (Box 66)
    - Let's Measure Distance, Weight and Time, Winter 1958 (Box 66)
  - Cornell Extension Bulletins
    - Outline of the Relation of the Use of Lime to the Improvement of Soil, July 1916
    - Control of Vegetable Diseases, June 1917 (Box 98)
    - Grass and Clover Insects, July 1917 (Box 98)
    - How to Select Laying Hens, September 1917 (Box 98)
    - The European Corn Borer, February 1919 (Box 98)
    - Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics in New York During 1918, July 1919 (Box 67)
    - Community Songs, December 1921 (Box 98)
    - The Historical Pageant in the Rural Community, June 1922 (Box 98)
    - Soldering, January 1923 (Box 67)
    - The Flowers that Bloom in the Spring, March 1923 (Box 66)
    - The Extension Service, April 1923 (Box 104)
    - The Farm Bureau Community Committee and Program of Work, April 1923 (Box 67)
    - The Flower Garden, August 1923 (Box 98)
    - The Flower Garden (reprint), August 1923 (Box 98)
    - Food-Selection Score Card, October 1923 (Box 98)
    - Food-Value Chart, November 1923 (Box 98)
    - Play Production for the Country Theatre, April 1924 (Box 67)
    - How to Use Apples as Food, July 1924 (Box 67)
    - The Gummed-Paper Dress Form-parts II and III, July 1924 (Box 98)
    - Fitting the Farm Saws, September 1924 (Box 67)
    - Electric Washing Machines, December 1924 (Box 98)
    - Portable Electric Vacuum Cleaners, December 1924 (Box 98)
    - Milk as a Daily Food, March 1925 (Box 67)
    - The Effectiveness of Extension in Reaching Rural People, March 1925 (Box 67)
    - Simplifying Home Sewing, September 1925 (Box 98)
    - Health and Personal Appearance, June 1925 (Box 67)
    - The Gummed-Paper Dress Form, April 1926 (Box 98)
    - Artistry in Dress, June 1926 (Box 98)
    - Fitting and Using the Dress Form, June 1926 (Box 98)
    - Gummed-Paper Dress Form Making, Altering, Covering and Mounting, October 1926-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Feet and Shoes, November 1926 (Box 98)
    - Drafting and Adapting the One-Piece Pattern, September 1927 (Box 98)
    - Preservation of Foods, December 1927 (Box 67)
    - The Control of Aphids on House Plants, 1927 (Box 67)
    - Program for a Child-Study Club, September 1928 (Box 67)
    - The Art of Vegetable Cookery, February 1929 (Box 67)
    - Cake, July 1929 (Box 67)
    - The Planting and Care of Trees and Shrubs (reprint), September 1929 (Box 98)
    - The Roadside Market, June 1930 (Box 67)
    - Home Storage of Vegetables, August 1930 (Box 98)
    - The Progressive Home, November 1930 (Box 98)
    - Common Insects of the Household, January 1931 (Box 67)
    - The Behavior of Children and Adults, December 1931 (Box 67)
    - Foods for Pre-School Children, June 1932 (Box 98)
    - Eggs, June 1932 (Box 67)
    - Low Cost Food for Health, June 1932 (Box 67)
    - It Pays to Buy Food Wisely, June 1932 (Box 67)
    - The Decorative Use of Flowers, November 1932 (Box 67)
    - Subsistence Gardens, February 1933 (Box 67)
    - Reconditioning Furniture, April 1933 (Box 98)
    - Woody Plants that Tolerate Shade, September 1933 (Box 98)
    - Food Budget for Homemade Living, June 1933 (Box 98)
    - Slip Covers, June 1933 (Box 98)
    - Letters from a Homemaker to her Friend on Household Management, June 1933 (Box 98)
    - Letters from a Homemaker to her Friend on House Cleaning, June 1933 (Box 98)
    - Homemade Play Material, June 1933 (Box 67)
    - Home Canning, June 1933 (Box 67)
    - House Cleaning, June 1933 (Box 67)
    - Letters from a Homemaker To Her Friend on Kitchen Improvement, June 1933 (Box 104)
    - Jellies, Preserves, and Fruit Juices, August 1933 (Box 67)
    - Pools for Home Grounds, August 1933 (Box 67)
    - The Behavior of Children and Adults: Part I-Routine Behavior, April 1934-Revised (Box 104)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - Songs, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - Pickles and Relishes, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - Cornell Child Study Clubs-Secretary's Record Book, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - Cornell Child Study Clubs-Suggestions for Parents, Teachers, and Others who wish to Start a Child Study Group, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - A Reading List for Parents, June 1934 (Box 67)
    - Lawns Construction and Maintenance, June 1934 (Box 98)
    - Children's Clothing, June 1934 (Box 98)
    - Sex Education, June 1934 (Box 98)
    - Feeding Babies and Mothers of Babies, June 1934 (Box 98)
    - The Decorative Use of Flowers, June 1934-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Growing Up With Books, June 1934 (Box 104)
    - Clipped Hedges and Their Uses, January 1935 (Box 98)
    - Amateur Flower Shows, March 1935 (Box 98)
    - Home Canning, April 1935-Revised (Box 98)
    - A Moth-Proof, Gas-Tight Closet for the Storage of Clothing and Other Woolens, June 1935 (Box 98)
    - Clothing for Children, August 1935 (Box 67)
    - How to Control your Weight, August 1935 (Box 67)
    - Growing Up With Books, September 1935-Reprint (Box 98)
    - The Purchasing of Sheets and Pillow Cases, September 1935 (Box 67)
    - Guidance and Punishment:Some Contrasts, October 1935 (Box 104)
    - Making or Marring the Child's Personality Through Emotional Experience, November 1935 (Box 104)
    - Pickles and Relishes, April 1936-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Feeding Pre-School Children, May 1936 (Box 67)
    - The Development of a Successful Kitchen, June 1936 (Box 67)
    - List of Publications, August 1936-Revised (Box 98)
    - Spot and Stain Removal, September 1936 (Box 67)
    - A Useful Supply of Kitchenware, September 1936 (Box 98)
    - Fitting and Using the Dress Form, October 1936-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Letters from a Homemaker to her Friend on House Cleaning, January 1937-Reprint (Box 104)
    - Games for 4H Clubs, Home Bureaus, and Groups in the Home, February 1937 (Box 104)
    - Common Insects of the Flower Garden, March 1937 (Box 98)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, April 1937-Reprint (Box 104)
    - Selection of Electrical Equipment for the Home, June 1937-Revised (Box 98)
    - Home and School Lighting, June 1937 (Box 98)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, June 1937-Revised (Box 104)
    - List of Publications, August 1937-Revised (Box 98)
    - Pickles and Relishes, October 1937-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Christmas Decorations, November 1937 (Box 104)
    - Sex Education, November 1937-Reprint (Box 104)
    - The Arrangement of Home Furnishings for Comfort, Convenience and Beauty, April 1938 (Box 98)
    - Your Money's Worth in Furniture, May 1938-Revised (Box 98)
    - Milk and Cheese, May 1938 (Box 67)
    - Cornell Family Life Study Clubs, June 1938-Revised (Box 98)
    - Reconditioning Furniture, June 1938-Revised (Box 98)
    - Kitchen Storage Space, November 1938 (Box 98)
    - We Can Kill a Beef or Veal, December 1938-Reprint (Box 99)
    - Potato Growing in New York, December 1938-Revised (Box 99)
    - Land Use in New York, April 1939 (Box 99)
    - Grinding the Farm Tools, May 1939-Reprint (Box 99)
    - Cornell Poultry Range Shelter, May 1939-Reprint (Box 99)
    - How to Make Slip Covers, June 1939 (Box 98)
    - Guidance: The Case of Ronald, September 1939 (Box 98)
    - Working Principles in Child Guidance, November 1939 (Box 104)
    - The Purchasing of Sheets and Pillow Cases, April 1940-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Making or Marring the Child's Personality Through Emotional Experience, April 1940-Reprint (Box 98)
    - The Development of a Successful Kitchen, May 1940-Revised (Box 98)
    - Starting Vegetable Plants, October 1940 (Box 67)
    - Choose a Play and How to Write One, November 1940 (Box 67)
    - Eat Apples, December 1940 (Box 67)
    - Spot and Stain Removal, May 1941-Revised (Box 98)
    - Woody Plants for Shady Places, June 1941 (Box 98)
    - Braided Rugs, June 1941 (Box 104)
    - The Home Lawn, September 1941 (Box 98)
    - Meals for Many, February 1942 (Box 98)
    - A Reading List For Parents, February 1942-Revised (Box 98)
    - Curtains and Draperies, March 1942 (Box 98)
    - Buying Food for the Family, July 1942 (Box 98)
    - List of Publications, July 1942-Revised (Box 98)
    - The Woman and Her Posture, September 1942 (Box 98)
    - Feeding Pre-School Children, October 1942-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Keeping Clothes Wearable, October 1942 (Box 67)
    - Wise Use and Care of an Electric Refrigerator, January 1943-Revised (Box 104)
    - How to Make Your Clothes Successful, March 1943 (Box 67)
    - Cooking Dehydrated Vegetables, March 1943 (Box 98)
    - Canning at Home, March 1943 (Box 98)
    - Linoleum & Felt-Base Floor Coverings, May 1943 (Box 67)
    - Outdoor Fireplaces, June 1943 (Box 67)
    - The Home Freezing of Farm Products, June 1943 (Box 104)
    - Drying Fruits and Vegetables at Home, July 1943 (Box 67)
    - The Home Repair of Electrical Equipment, July 1943 (Box 67)
    - Home Care of the Sick, September 1943 (Box 67)
    - Partial Covers to Protect Chairs, September 1943 (Box 67)
    - The Gummed Tape Dress Form, 1943 (Box 98)
    - List of Publications, January 1944-Revised (Box 98)
    - Kerosene Stoves, January 1944 (Box 67)
    - Victory Gardening, January 1944 (Box 104)
    - Buying and Care of Curtains, Slip Covers, and Draperies, March 1944 (Box 67)
    - By Your Own Upholsterer, June 1944 (Box 67)
    - An Accounting System for a Frozen-Food Locker Plant, June 1944 (Box 67)
    - Soap and Water Softeners, June 1944 (Box 67)
    - Be Your Own Upholsterer, June 1944 (Box 104)
    - Using the Home Freezer, November 1944 (Box 67)
    - Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, November 1944-Reprinted (Box 104)
    - Soybeans, February 1945 (Box 67)
    - Food-Value Chart, February 1945 (Box 67)
    - Electric Motor (Box 67)
    - Three Centuries of Furniture, March 1945 (Box 67)
    - Handling Cloth, June 1945 (Box 67)
    - The Returning Serviceman and His Family, August 1945 (Box 67)
    - How To Glue Furniture, September 1945 (Box 67)
    - Felt Hats, January 1946 (Box 67)
    - Foods from the Freezer: Precooked and Prepared, March 1946 (Box 67)
    - Some Common Edible and Poisonous Mushrooms, June 1946-Revised (Box 104)
    - Progress of the New York State Extension Service, July 1946 (Box 67)
    - Guidance and Punishment: Some Contrasts, July 1946-Reprint (Box 98)
    - How to Repair Wood Finishes, July 1946-Reprint (Box 67)
    - The Arrangement of Home Furnishings, July 1946-Reprint (Box 67)
    - How to Make Lampshades(oversized bulletin), August 1946 (Box 67)
    - Apples, January 1947 (Box 67)
    - Fruit Ices, January 1947 (Box 67)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, January 1947 (Box 104)
    - Home Values Test for Family Members, March 1947 (Box 67)
    - A Dairyman's Dozen, March 1947 (Box 67)
    - Make it Your House, March 1947 (Box 67)
    - Living with Baby, May 1947 (Box 67)
    - Canning Low-Acid Vegetables at Home, May 1947 (Box 67)
    - Introducing Frozen Elderberries, August 1947 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, October 1947-Reprint (Box 104)
    - Building a Home Freezer, January 1948-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Selecting a Building Site for Farm, Village, or City Homes, June 1948 (Box 98)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, September 1948-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Farm Women Look at the Home Bureau, September 1948 (Box 67)
    - Color in the Home, 1948 (Box 67)
    - Hand-Finishing Your Dress, October 1948 (Box 67)
    - Make Your Own Chair Covers(oversized bulletin, October 1948 (Box 67)
    - The Arrangement of Home Furnishings, November 1948-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Let's Prepare a Publication, January 1949 (Box 67)
    - List of Publications, April 1949 (Box 67)
    - The Japanese Beetle, July 1949 (Box 98)
    - Pressing in Dressmaking, August 1949 (Box 67)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, September 1949 (Box 104)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, September 1949 (Box 98)
    - Basting Your Dress, September 1949-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, November 1949 (Box 104)
    - Soaps and other Detergents, November 1949 (Box 67)
    - The Woman and Her Posture, February 1950-Reprint (Box 98)
    - The Home-Freezing of Farm Products, April 1950-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Simple Repairs of Upholstered Furniture, May 1950-Reprint (Box 104)
    - Wills and Other Ways to Transfer Property to Heirs, May 1950 (Box 67)
    - Simple Repairs of Upholstered Furniture, May 1950-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables, June 1950 (Box 67)
    - Meals for Paying Guests, July 1950 (Box 67)
    - Household Cleaning, August 1950 (Box 67)
    - Tomatoes the Year 'Round, August 1950 (Box 104)
    - The Adolescent: Physical Development, September 1950-Reprint (Box 98)
    - Spot and Stain Removal, September 1950-Reprint (Box 98)
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, November 1950 (Box 98)
    - Three Centuries of Furniture, November 1950-Revised (Box 67)
    - Outdoor Fireplaces, November 1950-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Landscape Steep Slopes, November 1950-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Good Cooking with Dry Milk, February 1951 (Box 67)
    - Home-Grown Lumber for Farm Buildings, February 1951 (Box 98)
    - Party Service, March 1951 (Box 104)
    - Let Your Kitchen Arrangement Work for You, April 1951 (Box 67)
    - Modern Hooked Rugs (oversized bulletin), April 1951 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, April 1951-Reprint (Box 104)
    - Jellies and Jams, May 1951 (Box 67)
    - Center for Your Work and Leisure, May 1951 (Box 67, 104)
    - Marmalades, Preserves, Conserves, and Butters, June 1951 (Box 104)
    - Molasses, July 1951 (Box 67)
    - Home Care of the Sick, July 1951 (Box 67)
    - Kitchen Cupboards That Simplify Storage, July 1951-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Foods from the Freezer: Precooked and Prepared, August 1951-Revised (Box 104)
    - Bedding, September 1951 (Box 67)
    - Helping Michael to Help Himself, September 1951 (Box 67)
    - Homemade Sauerkraut, September 1951 (Box 67)
    - How to Make Draperies, September 1951 (Box 67)
    - Carpentry Tools, October 1951 (Box 67)
    - Culinary Herbs, October 1951 (Box 67)
    - Driveways and Sidewalks, November 1951-Reprint (Box 67)
    - You Take It From Here, November 1951 (Box 98)
    - Gardening For Better Living, February 1952 (Box 104)
    - Growing Older, February 1952 (Box 67)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, February 1952-Reprint (Box 67)
    - Soldering, March 1952 (Box 67)
    - Repair of Innerspring Cushions, March 1952 (Box 67)
    - The Japanese Beetle, April 1952-Revised (Box 104)
    - Safe Home Wiring and Electric Cords, May 1952 (Box 104)
    - Good Cooking with Dry Milk, May 1952-Reprint (Box 67)
    - These Are Working Mothers, June 1952 (Box 98)